<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<r xmlns="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xsi:schemaLocation="http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2 http://pear.php.net/dtd/rest.release2.xsd">
    <p xlink:href="/rest/p/runkit">runkit</p>
    <c>zenovich.github.io/pear</c>
    <v>1.0.1</v>
    <a>1.0.1</a>
    <mp>4.0.0</mp>
    <st>stable</st>
    <l>PHP</l>
    <m></m>
    <s>For all those things you.... probably shouldn't have been doing anyway....</s>
    <d>Replace, rename, and remove user defined functions and classes.
Define customized superglobal variables for general purpose use.
Execute code in restricted environment (sandboxing).</d>
    <da>2010-10-03 19:35:25</da>
    <n>
New features:
    + The patch made by David Sklar was applied to support creation and changing of static methods.
      The new user-level const &quot;RUNKIT_ACC_STATIC&quot; was introduced.
    + An ability to import static class properties was added.
      The new user-level const &quot;RUNKIT_IMPORT_CLASS_STATIC_PROPS&quot; was introduced.
    + An ability to apply a closure to a sandbox in PHP 5.3+ by calling the call_user_func method was added.

Main bug-fixes:
    * Fixes of issues with importing constant arrays into properties and constants
    * Fixes of issues with importing functions or methods having static variables inside them
    * The behaviour that old methods had been always overridden by new ones independently from
      the RUNKIT_IMPORT_OVERRIDE flag was corrected
    * Compatibility with 5.3+ in zts mode
    * runkit_function_* functions were fixed with the patch from Keisial at gmail dot com
      (see the second comment from http://pecl.php.net/bugs/bug.php?id=14086)
    * The reverting of protected methods via runkit_method_copy was corrected, the segmentation fault
      on calling restored method was eliminated
    * Elimination of the segmentation-fault on exit after restoring modified internal functions
      (see also http://pecl.php.net/bugs/bug.php?id=11632)
    * Correction for the situation when a method or function having static variables in itself
      and copied by runkit crashes afterwards on calling if the original method or function was removed
    * The issue that the runkit used to create new methods with lowercase names was fixed, tests were extended
    * Methods' prototype detection was fixed
 </n>
    <f>56719</f>
    <g>https://zenovich.github.io/pear/get/runkit-1.0.1</g>
    <x xlink:href="package.1.0.1.xml"/>
</r>